This is number two of three of my
favorite eating devices. So, this is a
tablet that you can use for reading
documents, taking notes, or using as a
scratch pad. So, in terms of the OS,
it's pretty much the same as the books
[music] palm. It runs Android, so you
can customize it however you want. So,
what I mostly use this for is reading
things that are in an A4 size. For
example, [music] textbooks, documents,
and sheet music, like guitar and piano.
I use this cuz you can mark it up as
well. And it's also really nice to use
as a scratch [music] pad because the pen
that it comes with is really responsive
and it's nice to draw on. The build
quality on this is also really nice.
It's really thin. The pen has a magnetic
holder right next to it and there's even
a backlight. If you're looking for
something like that where you can back
[music] it up and not be scared of
losing your actual journals, I think
this is a really good solution.